James Kolbe Papers, 1958-2006 (bulk 1985-2006)
University of Arizona Libraries, Special Collections
- Subgroup 2: Congressional Activities, 1980-2006
  - Legislative Activity Files, Series 2: 1984-2006
    - 104th Congress, 1986-2000
      - H.R 210- Privatization of the United States Postal Service, 1995-1996 (Box 46, Folder 7)
      - H.R. 361- Omnibus Export Administration Act, 1992-1996 (Box 46, Folder 8)
      - H.R. 483- Medicare Select, 1994-1995 (Box 46, Folder 9)
      - H.R. 534- One Dollar Coin Act (1 of 2), 1995-1996 (Box 46, Folder 10)
      - H.R. 534- One Dollar Coin Act (2 of 2), 1995-1996 (Box 46, Folder 11)
      - H.R. 927- Cuban Liberty and Democratic Solidarity Act, 1995-1996 (Box 46, Folder 12)
      - H.R. 1462- Morris K. Udall Parkinson's Research, Assistance, and Education Act, 1995 (Box 46, Folder 13)
      - H.R. 2976- Patient Right to Know Act, 1996 (Box 46, Folder 14)
      - H.R. 3103- The Health Coverage Availability and Affordability Act (1 of 2), 1996 (Box 46, Folder 15)
      - H.R. 3103- The Health Coverage Availability and Affordability Act (2 of 2), 1996 (Box 46, Folder 16)
      - H.R. 3107- Iran and Libya Sanctions Act, 1996 (Box 46, Folder 17)
      - H.R. 3161- Most Favored Nation Treatment of Romania, 1996 (Box 46, Folder 18)
      - H.R. 3654- The Textile and Apparel Global Competitiveness Act, 1996-1997 (Box 46, Folder 19)
      - H.R. 3666- Section 421 of Cray/Ucar Supercomputer (1 of 2), 1996 (Box 46, Folder 20)
      - H.R. 3666- Section 421 of Cray/Ucar Supercomputer (2 of 2), 1996 (Box 46, Folder 21)
      - Immigration, 1996 (Box 46, Folder 22)
      - Immigration and Naturalization Service border checkpoints, 1995-1996 (Box 46, Folder 23)
      - Iran, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 1)
      - Israel, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 2)
      - Japan, Cray computers, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 3)
      - Japan, Insurance, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 4)
      - Japan, Semiconductors, 1994-1996 (Box 47, Folder 5)
      - Kolbe, Jim legislative profile, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 6)
      - Korea, 1995 (Box 47, Folder 7)
      - Medicare (1 of 2), 1995 (Box 47, Folder 8)
      - Medicare (2 of 2), 1995 (Box 47, Folder 9)
      - Medicare subvention, 1996-1997 (Box 47, Folder 10)
      - Mexico- Acceleration of tariff reductions, 1994-1995 (Box 47, Folder 11)
      - Mexico- Border environment, 1992-1996 (Box 47, Folder 12)
      - Mexico- Briefing book, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 13)
      - Mexico- CEMEX (1 of 3), 1995-1996 (Box 47, Folder 14)
      - Mexico- CEMEX (2 of 3), 1995-1996 (Box 47, Folder 15)
      - Mexico- CEMEX (3 of 3), 1995-1996 (Box 47, Folder 16)
      - Mexico- Drugs, 1996 (Box 47, Folder 17)
      - Mexico- Loan Guarantee package (1 of 3), 1995 (Box 47, Folder 18)
      - Mexico- Loan Guarantee package (2 of 3), 1995 (Box 47, Folder 19)
      - Mexico- Loan Guarantee package (3 of 3), 1995 (Box 47, Folder 20)
      - Mexico- Metalclad Corporation, 1995-1996 (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - Mexico- Peso crisis (1 of 2), 1986-1995 (Box 48, Folder 2)
      - Mexico- Peso crisis (2 of 2), 1986-1995 (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - Mexico- Tomato seasonal tariff rate quota (1 of 3), 1995-2000 (Box 48, Folder 4)
      - Mexico- Tomato seasonal tariff rate quota (2 of 3), 1995-2000 (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - Mexico- Tomato seasonal tariff rate quota (3 of 3), 1995-2000 (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - Mexico-United States Interparlimentary meeting discussion papers, 1996 (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - North American Free Trade Agreement (1 of 3), 1993-1997 (Box 48, Folder 8)
      - North American Free Trade Agreement (2 of 3), 1993-1997 (Box 48, Folder 9)
      - North American Free Trade Agreement (3 of 3), 1993-1997 (Box 48, Folder 10)
      - North American Free Trade Agreement- Mexico tomato imports, 1995-1996 (Box 48, Folder 11)
      - NEXRAD site, 1994-1995 (Box 48, Folder 12)
      - One Dollar Coin (1 of 2), 1995 (Box 48, Folder 13)
      - One Dollar Coin (2 of 2), 1995 (Box 48, Folder 14)
      - Page Board, 1995-1996 (Box 48, Folder 15)
      - Research, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 1)
      - Ricky Ray Hemophilia Act, 1995-2000 (Box 49, Folder 2)
      - Social Security (1 of 4), 1995-1996 (Box 49, Folder 3)
      - Social Security (2 of 4), 1995-1996 (Box 49, Folder 4)
      - Social Security (3 of 4), 1995-1996 (Box 49, Folder 5)
      - Social Security (4 of 4), 1995-1996 (Box 49, Folder 6)
      - Social Security Reform (1 of 2), 1996 (Box 49, Folder 7)
      - Social Security Reform (2 of 2), 1996 (Box 49, Folder 8)
      - Timber salvage, 1995-1996 (Box 49, Folder 9)
      - Transatlantic Policy Network, 1995-1996 (Box 49, Folder 10)
      - Tucson Federal Courthouse, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 11)
      - Unfunded mandates, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 12)
      - Unified Port Management, 1996 (Box 49, Folder 13)
      - Unified Parcel Service, 1995 (Box 49, Folder 14)
      - United States Consulate in Hermosillo (1 of 2), 1995 (Box 50, Folder 1)
      - United States Consulate in Hermosillo (2 of 2), 1995 (Box 50, Folder 2)
      - United States-Japan Trade (1 of 2), 1993-1999 (Box 50, Folder 3)
      - United States-Japan Trade (2 of 2), 1993-1999 (Box 50, Folder 4)
      - United States-Mexico high level contact group on drug control, 1996-1997 (Box 50, Folder 5)
      - United States-Mexico interparliamentary conference briefing book (1 of 2), 1995 (Box 50, Folder 6)
      - United States-Mexico interparliamentary conference briefing book (2 of 2), 1995 (Box 50, Folder 7)
      - United States-Mexico interparliamentary group meeting briefing book (1 of 2), 1996 (Box 50, Folder 8)
      - United States-Mexico interparliamentary group meeting briefing book (2 of 2), 1996 (Box 50, Folder 9)
      - Viper Militia Case, 1996 (Box 50, Folder 10)
      - Welfare reform, 1995-1996 (Box 50, Folder 11)
    - 105th Congress, 1991-2002
      - American Heritage Rivers, 1997-1998 (Box 50, Folder 12)
      - Allied Signal, 1997 (Box 50, Folder 13)
      - Appropriations Committee (1 of 8), 1995-1998 (Box 50, Folder 14)
      - Appropriations Committee (2 of 8), 1995-1998 (Box 50, Folder 15)
      - Appropriations Committee (3 of 8), 1995-1998 (Box 51, Folder 1)
      - Appropriations Committee (4 of 8), 1995-1998 (Box 51, Folder 2)
      - Appropriations Committee (5 of 8), 1995-1998 (Box 51, Folder 3)
      - Appropriations Committee (6 of 8), 1995-1998 (Box 51, Folder 4)
      - Appropriations Committee (7 of 8), 1995-1998 (Box 51, Folder 5)
      - Appropriations Committee (8 of 8), 1995-1998 (Box 51, Folder 6)
      - Appropriations Committee, Commerce, Justice, Science and Related Agencies subcommittees (1 of 6), 1995-1998 (Box 51, Folder 7)
      - Appropriations Committee, Commerce, Justice, Science and Related Agencies subcommittees (2 of 6), 1995-1998 (Box 51, Folder 8)
      - Appropriations Committee, Commerce, Justice, Science and Related Agencies subcommittees (3 of 6), 1995-1998 (Box 51, Folder 9)
      - Appropriations Committee, Commerce, Justice, Science and Related Agencies subcommittees (4 of 6), 1995-1998 (Box 51, Folder 10)
      - Appropriations Committee, Commerce, Justice, Science and Related Agencies subcommittees (5 of 6), 1995-1998 (Box 51, Folder 11)
      - Appropriations Committee, Commerce, Justice, Science and Related Agencies subcommittees (6 of 6), 1995-1998 (Box 51, Folder 12)
      - Appropriations Committee, Foreign Operations, Export Financing and Related Agencies subcommittee (1 of 2), 1996-1998 (Box 52, Folder 1)
      - Appropriations Committee, Foreign Operations, Export Financing and Related Agencies subcommittee (2 of 2), 1996-1998 (Box 52, Folder 2)
      - Appropriations Committee, Subcommittee on Treasury, Postal Service and General Government, 1997-1998 (Box 52, Folder 3)
      - Arizona Citrus, 1997 (Box 52, Folder 4)
      - Arizona Health Care Cost Containment System, 1993-1998 (Box 52, Folder 5)
      - Arizona military bases, 1997-1998 (Box 52, Folder 6)
      - Asarco Rosemont ranch land exchange, 1997-1998 (Box 52, Folder 7)
      - BHP/Asarco solid waste, 1997 (Box 52, Folder 8)
      - Briefing book- Africa, 1997-1998 (Box 52, Folder 9)
      - Briefing book- August recess (1 of 2), 1997 (Box 52, Folder 10)
      - Briefing book- August recess (2 of 2), 1997 (Box 52, Folder 11)
      - Briefing book- China most favored nation, 1997 (Box 52, Folder 12)
      - Briefing book- 2nd Session recess (1 of 2), 1998 (Box 52, Folder 13)
      - Briefing book- 2nd Session recess (2 of 2), 1998 (Box 52, Folder 14)
      - Cactus Ferruginous Pygmy Owl, 1998 (Box 52, Folder 15)
      - Central Arizona Project (1 of 6), 1995-1999 (Box 52, Folder 16)
      - Central Arizona Project (2 of 6), 1995-1999 (Box 53, Folder 1)
      - Central Arizona Project (3 of 6), 1995-1999 (Box 53, Folder 2)
      - Central Arizona Project (4 of 6), 1995-1999 (Box 53, Folder 3)
      - Central Arizona Project (5 of 6), 1995-1999 (Box 53, Folder 4)
      - Central Arizona Project (6 of 6), 1995-1999 (Box 53, Folder 5)
      - Chile, 1997-1998 (Box 53, Folder 6)
      - China most favored nation trading status, 1997 (Box 53, Folder 7)
      - Clean Air Act Amendment (1 of 2), 1991-1998 (Box 53, Folder 8)
      - Clean Air Act Amendment (2 of 2), 1991-1998 (Box 53, Folder 9)
      - Commission for Environmental Cooperation (1 of 2), 1997-1998 (Box 53, Folder 10)
      - Commission for Environmental Cooperation (2 of 2), 1997-1998 (Box 53, Folder 11)
      - Congressional Record Statements, 1997-1998 (Box 53, Folder 12)
      - Contraceptive Coverage Act, 1997-1998 (Box 53, Folder 13)
      - Co-sponsor solicitation letters, incoming (1 of 6), 1996-1998 (Box 53, Folder 14)
      - Co-sponsor solicitation letters, incoming (2 of 6), 1996-1998 (Box 54, Folder 1)
      - Co-sponsor solicitation letters, incoming (3 of 6), 1996-1998 (Box 54, Folder 2)
      - Co-sponsor solicitation letters, incoming (4 of 6), 1996-1998 (Box 54, Folder 3)
      - Co-sponsor solicitation letters, incoming (5 of 6), 1996-1998 (Box 54, Folder 4)
      - Co-sponsor solicitation letters, incoming (6 of 6), 1996-1998 (Box 54, Folder 5)
      - Co-sponsor solicitation letters, outgoing, 1995-1998 (Box 54, Folder 6)
      - Counter-Narcotics Policy Review Act, 1993-1997 (Box 54, Folder 7)
      - E-Rate Program, 1998 (Box 54, Folder 8)
      - Food and Drug Administration reform (1 of 2), 1997 (Box 54, Folder 9)
      - Food and Drug Administration reform (2 of 2), 1997 (Box 54, Folder 10)
      - Fort Huachuca, 1997-1998 (Box 54, Folder 11)
      - Fort Sill-Chiricahua, Apache legislation, 1997 (Box 54, Folder 12)
      - Fort Sill-Chiricahua, Warm Springs/Apache Tribe Resolution, 1997 (Box 54, Folder 13)
      - Gila River Indian community, 1997-1998 (Box 54, Folder 14)
      - Gila Valley and Franklin Irrigation, 1997-1999 (Box 54, Folder 15)
      - Healthcare, 1997-1998 (Box 54, Folder 16)
      - Hefley Amendment, 1998 (Box 54, Folder 17)
      - High intensity drug trafficking area, 1998 (Box 54, Folder 18)
      - High level Commission on International Narcotics Control, 1997 (Box 54, Folder 19)
      - H.Con.Res. 23- Expressing respect and affection for the Flag of the United States, 1997-1998 (Box 54, Folder 20)
      - H.Con.Res. 332- Expressing the sense of Congress regarding the policy of the Forest Service toward recreational shooting and archery ranges on federal land, 1998 (Box 54, Folder 21)
      - H.Con.Res. 469- Expressing the sense of the House of Representatives regarding assistance to Mexico to combat wildfires, 1998 (Box 54, Folder 22)
      - H.J.Res. 52- Balanced Budget Act Tax Limitations, 1997-1998 (Box 54, Folder 23)
      - H.J.Res. 78- Religious Freedom Amendment, 1998 (Box 54, Folder 24)
      - House Page Board (1 of 2), 1998 (Box 55, Folder 1)
      - House Page Board (2 of 2), 1998 (Box 55, Folder 2)
      - H.R. 695- Export Controls on Encryption, 1998-2000 (Box 55, Folder 3)
      - H.R. 750- Hong Kong Reversion Act, 1997 (Box 55, Folder 4)
      - H.R. 901- American Land Sovereignty Protection Act, 1997-1999 (Box 55, Folder 5)
      - H.R. 1174- One Dollar Coin Act, 1995-1997 (Box 55, Folder 6)
      - H.R. 1317- Counter-Narcotics Policy Review Act, 1997 (Box 55, Folder 7)
      - H.R. 1371- Country of Origin Labeling on Meat and Meat Products (1 of 2), 1997-1998 (Box 55, Folder 8)
      - H.R. 1371- Country of Origin Labeling on Meat and Meat Products (2 of 2), 1997-1998 (Box 55, Folder 9)
      - H.R. 1432- African Growth and Opportunity Act (1 of 2), 1997-1998 (Box 55, Folder 10)
      - H.R. 1432- African Growth and Opportunity Act (2 of 2), 1997-1998 (Box 55, Folder 11)
      - H.R. 1486- Counter- Narcotics Policy Review Act, 1997 (Box 55, Folder 12)
      - H.R. 1868 Amendment, 1997 (Box 55, Folder 13)
      - H.R. 2107- Istook Amendment, 1997-1998 (Box 55, Folder 14)
      - H.R. 2275- Endangered Species Conservation and Management Act, 1995-1998 (Box 55, Folder 15)
      - H.R. 2431- Freedom from Religious Persecution Act, 1998 (Box 55, Folder 16)
      - H.R. 2493- Forage Improvement Act, 1997-1998 (Box 55, Folder 17)
      - H.R. 3654- Agricultural Sanctions, 1997-1998 (Box 55, Folder 18)
      - H.R. 4116- Border Visa Simplification Act, 1998 (Box 55, Folder 19)
      - H.R. 4276- Kolbe Amendment, 1998 (Box 55, Folder 20)
      - H.R. 4558- Welfare Technical Corrections Bill, 1998 (Box 56, Folder 1)
      - H.R. 4570- The Omnibus National Parks and Public Lands Act, 1998 (Box 56, Folder 2)
      - House Republican Legislative Priorities for the 105th Congress, 1996-1999 (Box 56, Folder 3)
      - Impeachment- President Clinton (1 of 4), 1998 (Box 56, Folder 4)
      - Impeachment- President Clinton (2 of 4), 1998 (Box 56, Folder 5)
      - Impeachment- President Clinton (3 of 4), 1998 (Box 56, Folder 6)
      - Impeachment- President Clinton (4 of 4), 1998 (Box 56, Folder 7)
      - Indian Health Service, 1998 (Box 56, Folder 8)
      - Indian Health Service- Federal Medical assistance percentage, 1998 (Box 56, Folder 9)
      - International Arid Lands Consortium, 1997-1998 (Box 56, Folder 10)
      - Japan pharmaceuticals, 1998 (Box 56, Folder 11)
      - Kodak- Fuji case, 1995-1998 (Box 56, Folder 12)
      - Korea, 1997-1998 (Box 56, Folder 13)
      - Kyoto Climate Change Protocol, 1997-2001 (Box 56, Folder 14)
      - Lebanon travel restrictions, 1997 (Box 56, Folder 15)
      - Malpai borderlands group, 1996-1998 (Box 56, Folder 16)
      - Medicare (1 of 5), 1997-1999 (Box 56, Folder 17)
      - Medicare (2 of 5), 1997-1999 (Box 56, Folder 18)
      - Medicare (3 of 5), 1997-1999 (Box 56, Folder 19)
      - Medicare (4 of 5), 1997-1999 (Box 57, Folder 1)
      - Medicare (5 of 5), 1997-1999 (Box 57, Folder 2)
      - Mexico certification (1 of 2), 1996-2001 (Box 57, Folder 3)
      - Mexico certification (2 of 2), 1996-2001 (Box 57, Folder 4)
      - Morris K. Udall Foundation (1 of 5), 1997-1998 (Box 57, Folder 5)
      - Morris K. Udall Foundation (2 of 5), 1997-1998 (Box 57, Folder 6)
      - Morris K. Udall Foundation (3 of 5), 1997-1998 (Box 57, Folder 7)
      - Morris K. Udall Foundation (4 of 5), 1997-1998 (Box 57, Folder 8)
      - Morris K. Udall Foundation (5 of 5), 1997-1998 (Box 57, Folder 9)
      - North American Free Trade Agreement (1 of 3), 1996-2001 (Box 57, Folder 10)
      - North American Free Trade Agreement (2 of 3), 1996-2001 (Box 57, Folder 11)
      - North American Free Trade Agreement (3 of 3), 1996-2001 (Box 57, Folder 12)
      - North American Free Trade Agreement- Briefing book, 1997 (Box 57, Folder 13)
      - North American Free Trade Agreement- Myths and Realities talking points, 1997-1998 (Box 58, Folder 1)
      - National Commission on Retirement Policy (1 of 7), 1997-1998 (Box 58, Folder 2)
      - National Commission on Retirement Policy (2 of 7), 1997-1998 (Box 58, Folder 3)
      - National Commission on Retirement Policy (3 of 7), 1997-1998 (Box 58, Folder 4)
      - National Commission on Retirement Policy (4 of 7), 1997-1998 (Box 58, Folder 5)
      - National Commission on Retirement Policy (5 of 7), 1997-1998 (Box 58, Folder 6)
      - National Commission on Retirement Policy (6 of 7), 1997-1998 (Box 58, Folder 7)
      - National Commission on Retirement Policy (7 of 7), 1997-1998 (Box 58, Folder 8)
      - The National Parks Capital Improvements Act, 1997 (Box 58, Folder 9)
      - One Dollar Coin Act (1 of 2), 1991-1997 (Box 58, Folder 10)
      - One Dollar Coin Act (2 of 2), 1991-1997 (Box 58, Folder 11)
      - Presidential Position Votes, 1998 (Box 58, Folder 12)
      - Public Pension Reform Caucus, 1997-1998 (Box 58, Folder 13)
      - Safford, Arizona, 1997-1998 (Box 58, Folder 14)
      - Saguaro National Monument expansions (1 of 2), 1992-2002 (Box 58, Folder 15)
      - Saguaro National Monument expansions (2 of 2), 1992-2002 (Box 59, Folder 1)
      - San Carlos Apache Tribe Water Rights (1 of 6), 1997-1998 (Box 59, Folder 2)
      - San Carlos Apache Tribe Water Rights (2 of 6), 1997-1998 (Box 59, Folder 3)
      - San Carlos Apache Tribe Water Rights (3 of 6), 1997-1998 (Box 59, Folder 4)
      - San Carlos Apache Tribe Water Rights (4 of 6), 1997-1998 (Box 59, Folder 5)
      - San Carlos Apache Tribe Water Rights (5 of 6), 1997-1998 (Box 59, Folder 6)
      - San Carlos Apache Tribe Water Rights (6 of 6), 1997-1998 (Box 59, Folder 7)
      - Santa Cruz River, 1996-1997 (Box 59, Folder 8)
      - Social Security (1 of 6), 1997-2000 (Box 59, Folder 9)
      - Social Security (2 of 6), 1997-2000 (Box 59, Folder 10)
      - Social Security (3 of 6), 1997-2000 (Box 59, Folder 11)
      - Social Security (4 of 6), 1997-2000 (Box 59, Folder 12)
      - Social Security (5 of 6), 1997-2000 (Box 60, Folder 1)
      - Social Security (6 of 6), 1997-2000 (Box 60, Folder 2)
      - Social Security Task Force, 1998 (Box 60, Folder 3)
      - Special Occupational tax, 1998 (Box 60, Folder 4)
      - Taxes (1 of 2), 1994-2000 (Box 60, Folder 5)
      - Taxes (2 of 2), 1994-2000 (Box 60, Folder 6)
      - United States Currency Paper Audit, 1997 (Box 60, Folder 7)
      - Wild and Scenic Rivers, 1996-1998 (Box 60, Folder 8)
    - 106th Congress, 1996-2002
      - Access to Quality Care Act, 1999-2001 (Box 60, Folder 9)
      - Appropriations Committee- Agriculture appropriations (1 of 4), 1999-2000 (Box 60, Folder 10)
      - Appropriations Committee- Agriculture appropriations (2 of 4), 1999-2000 (Box 60, Folder 11)
      - Appropriations Committee- Agriculture appropriations (3 of 4), 1999-2000 (Box 60, Folder 12)
      - Appropriations Committee- Agriculture appropriations (4 of 4), 1999-2000 (Box 60, Folder 13)
      - Appropriations Committee- Commerce, Justice, Science and related agencies (1 of 5), 1998-2000 (Box 60, Folder 14)
      - Appropriations Committee- Commerce, Justice, Science and related agencies (2 of 5), 1998-2000 (Box 60, Folder 15)
      - Appropriations Committee- Commerce, Justice, Science and related agencies (3 of 5), 1998-2000 (Box 61, Folder 1)
      - Appropriations Committee- Commerce, Justice, Science and related agencies (4 of 5), 1998-2000 (Box 61, Folder 2)
      - Appropriations Committee- Commerce, Justice, Science and related agencies (5 of 5), 1998-2000 (Box 61, Folder 3)
      - Appropriations Committee- Commerce, Justice, Science and related agencies, International Boundary and Water Commission, 1999 (Box 61, Folder 4)
      - Appropriations Committee- Commerce, Justice, Science and related agencies, WestCare Batterers Intervention Demonstration Project, 1998-1999 (Box 61, Folder 5)
      - Appropriations Committee- Department of Transportation requests (1 of 2), 1999 (Box 61, Folder 6)
      - Appropriations Committee- Department of Transportation requests (2 of 2), 1999 (Box 61, Folder 7)
      - Appropriations Committee- Foreign Operations, Export Financing and Related Programs, 1998-2000 (Box 61, Folder 8)
      - Appropriations Committee- Foreign Operations, Export Financing and Related Programs, American Education in Lebanon, 1999 (Box 61, Folder 9)
      - Appropriations Committee- Labor, Health and Human Services committee mark up, 2000 (Box 61, Folder 10)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on the Interior and related agencies (1 of 10), 1999-2000 (Box 61, Folder 11)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on the Interior and related agencies (2 of 10), 1999-2000 (Box 61, Folder 12)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on the Interior and related agencies (3 of 10), 1999-2000 (Box 61, Folder 13)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on the Interior and related agencies (4 of 10), 1999-2000 (Box 61, Folder 14)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on the Interior and related agencies (5 of 10), 1999-2000 (Box 61, Folder 15)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on the Interior and related agencies (6 of 10), 1999-2000 (Box 61, Folder 16)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on the Interior and related agencies (7 of 10), 1999-2000 (Box 62, Folder 1)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on the Interior and related agencies (8 of 10), 1999-2000 (Box 62, Folder 2)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on the Interior and related agencies (9 of 10), 1999-2000 (Box 62, Folder 3)
      - Appropriations Committee- Subcommittee on the Interior and related agencies (10 of 10), 1999-2000 (Box 62, Folder 4)
      - Appropriations Committee- Tactical Engagement Simulation System, 1999-2002 (Box 62, Folder 5)
      - Appropriations Committee- Treasury, Postal Service and related general government (1 of 3), 1998-2000 (Box 62, Folder 6)
      - Appropriations Committee- Treasury, Postal Service and related general government (2 of 3), 1998-2000 (Box 62, Folder 7)
      - Appropriations Committee- Treasury, Postal Service and related general government (3 of 3), 1998-2000 (Box 62, Folder 8)
      - Appropriations Committee- Treasury, Postal Service and related general government, Automated Commercial Environment, 1999-2000 (Box 62, Folder 9)
      - Appropriations Committee- Treasury, Postal Service and related general government, Federal Election Commission, 1999 (Box 62, Folder 10)
      - Appropriations Committee- Treasury, Postal Service and related general government, National Youth Anti-drug Media Campaign, 2000 (Box 62, Folder 11)
      - Appropriations Committee- Treasury, Postal Service and related general government, OMB circular A-110, 1999-2000 (Box 62, Folder 12)
      - Appropriations Committee- Treasury, Postal Service and related general government, Regulation to ensure data quality of Information used and disseminated by the Federal Government, 1999-2000 (Box 62, Folder 13)
      - Appropriations Committee- Treasury, Postal Service and related general government, United States Customs (1 of 2), 1999-2000 (Box 62, Folder 14)
      - Appropriations Committee- Treasury, Postal Service and related general government, United States Customs (2 of 2), 1999-2000 (Box 62, Folder 15)
      - Appropriations Committee- Treasury, Postal Service and related government, United States Customs Air and Marine Interdiction Program, 1999-2000 (Box 63, Folder 1)
      - Appropriations Committee- Treasury, Postal Service and related government, United States Postal Service (1 of 3), 1997-2000 (Box 63, Folder 2)
      - Appropriations Committee- Treasury, Postal Service and related government, United States Postal Service (2 of 3), 1997-2000 (Box 63, Folder 3)
      - Appropriations Committee- Treasury, Postal Service and related government, United States Postal Service (3 of 3), 1997-2000 (Box 63, Folder 4)
      - Appropriations Committee- Treasury, Postal Service and related government, White House and President's Park Comprehensive Design Plan, 1998-1999 (Box 63, Folder 5)
      - Appropriations Committee- Markups, 1999 (Box 63, Folder 6)
      - Appropriations Committee- Supplemental Appropriations, 1999-2000 (Box 63, Folder 7)